#### 535 OLDHIGHLANDS ST. HENDERSON, NV 89015 PHONE (505) 310-8973 E-MAIL JAMES.STRITE@GMAIL.COM

# JAMES F. STRITE

# OBJECTIVE

To support the growth and profitability of an organization that provides challenge, encourages advancement, and rewards achievement with the opportunity to utilize my substantial experience, organizational skills, and proven abilities in, customer service, information technology, public relations & management.

## UNIQUE QUALIFICATIONS

Information Systems Technician with 7+ years of professional experience with strong interpersonal guest and employee relation skills. Ability to implement excellent conflict intervention and resolution techniques. Strong customer satisfaction focus. Highly technically proficient in Mac OS and Windows, Office and all related software and hardware for either platform. Experience in Active Directory and SCCM. Possess an Associate Degree in Computers and Information Technology. Enjoy working with hardware in both building and repairing desktop computers. Have spent 7 years in a medical environment working hospital IT and the last two years in Radiology specifically.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Oct 2019-Mar 2020 Randstad/Gallagher Insurance

Las Vegas, NV

## Service Desk Analyst

- Responsible for providing general IT support remotely via a high-volume phone system for 35,000 employees and clients.
- Currently working 20-30 tickets a day in direct support of employees, resolving a number of IT issues regarding numerous Citrix and Windows based applications.
- Hardware and VPN support for claims adjusters working remotely and at numerous branch locations across the US and Internationally.
- Experienced in the use of SCCM, Active Directory and Citrix in the support of users in this environment.
- Able to support a strict metrics-based environment where call adherence and average call time are essential to effectively serving users.

Jan 2018-Oct 2019 Christus St. Vincent Regional Medical Center Santa Fe, NM

#### PACS Systems Analyst

- Responsible for the support and maintenance of the following systems McKesson PACS, McKesson CPACS, Powerscribe, Radimetrics, and Muse.
- Currently running 10-15 tickets a day troubleshooting a variety of issues involving, workstations, networking, and numerous servers.
- Worked extensively with the Epic and Cerner applications during a hospital wide

- EMR migration.
- Experienced in the use of Epic for a variety of daily troubleshooting tasks including, working HL7 error ques.
- Responsible for repairing and resending HL7 interface messages to push results through to Epic and all downstream systems.
- Experienced in the use of VM's and currently manage 20 servers for a variety of systems including PACS and CPACS. This includes updates, patches and security.
- Additional application support includes Bedwatch, Milestone Camera System, and Lifeimage.
- Responsible for emergency support for users and systems during off hours, weekends, and holidays.
- Responsible for server maintenance and security including updates, patches, and software specific utilities and services to provide a seamless customer experience.
- As a team we support and maintain up to a 100 dedicated PACS and CPACS workstations. This includes implementation of Active Directory policy, updates, anti-virus, and general upkeep and maintenance.
- Familiar in the support and use of Barco video cards, monitors and radiologist reading stations.
- Have led specific projects regarding system upgrades, additions, expansions and hardware and new software deployments.

March 2013-Jan 2018 Christus St. Vincent Regional Medical Center Santa Fe, NM

## Desktop Support Technician - Service Desk Technician Level II

- Take great pride in being part of a winning team and seeing the growth and success of the organization
- Able to work independently without supervision but respond and work well in a team-based environment and am able to take direction as well
- Worked in high-volume ticketing systems including, Footprints and Service Now. Running upwards of 15-20 tickets a day as a Desktop Tech and up to 100 as a Service Desk Tech.
- Have fulfilled an urgent on call role providing immediate support for medical staff during high pressure situations
- Always have maintained a high level of customer service and have received innumerable positive surveys during my time at Christus
- Experienced in basic network troubleshooting and support
- Provided advanced troubleshooting and support for a wide variety of software and hardware issues.
- Was responsible to manage incoming and emergent customer issues via a ticketing system
- Perform regular maintenance and repairs on desktops, laptops, printers, and scanners
- Organized and facilitated large scale moves and hardware deployments
- Utilize SCCM 2012 to image PC's and deploy software

- Provided remote support to offsite coders via Bomgar
- Provided hardware support for main hospital and all offsite clinics on a network consisting of 2000+ PC's and 600+ printers and scanners
- Promoted to Desktop Tech in 2015
- Answer incoming calls and emails and assist user's remotely using various remote tools
- Provided onsite hardware and software support for user's during evening hours
- Managed inventory and incoming freight for entire user base
- Assisted during a successful migration from XP to Windows 7 for over 2000 machines
- Responsible for server and interface monitoring and reporting for hospital network
- Maintained and performed tape backup's for hospital users
- Experienced in the use of Active Directory for managing user's and group memberships
- Experienced in the use of Cerner and its related applications as well as E Clinical Works, Epic.

## 2010-2012 Student SFCC Santa Fe, NM

- Graduated Fall 2012 with an Associates in Applied Science
- Highly proficient in Mac Os X and Windows
- Experienced with Microsoft Office on either platform
- Have had experience with networking, databases, virus, malware, and adware removal
- Very comfortable with portable hardware and devices and their related software
- Very comfortable with all related hardware for Mac or Windows
- Highly experienced in building and repairing desktop computers

## AWARDS RECEIVED

Obtained numerous kudos and WOW's from customers and co-workers for Christus St. Vincent 2013-2019.

#### **EDUCATION**

Fall 2012 Graduate SFCC – Computer and Information Technology AAS Elon College, Burlington NC. 1991-95

Summer 1991 Graduate Lake Highland Preparatory School, Orlando FL.